Ally!
Hang in there, Ally!
It doesn't have a core!
What's that sound?
Looks like the test succeeded.
I hope you all made the most
of your vacation in Yamato.
School Festa
Yes, thank you.
Karen had a good time, too.
She was able to see everyone
from the facility.
We brought back some snacks, but...
These steamed buns are great.
I can't stop eating them.
So what happened to the hunters?
They've been more or less
behaving since they got here.
The three of them are staying cooped up
in our special underground facility.
But they're refusing to give us
any crucial information.
Also, Warslarn HQ's intelligence division
found Vitaly Tynyanov's lab the other day.
What?
What about Vitaly?
Unfortunately, she had already left.
I see...
We tried to analyze the research data
that was left behind,
but the important parts had been erased.
Anyway, so long as Vitaly Tynyanov
remains on the loose,
we need to tighten security.
A joint task force of Slayers from various countries
will handle security during Garden's Festa.
Garden's Festa?
The Garden's Festa is an event which celebrates
the launching of the Little Garden.
It's a school festival of sorts.
Since the event will be open
to the general public,
we'll remain docked at United States Liberia's
San Gría Port for the duration.
This year's Garden's Festa
is going to be great.
I'll be doing a concert as a special event.
And I have a super-secret
special weapon for it.
Huh? What's that?
Secret means secret!
We're currently finishing up
the last preparations.
We're requisitioning any materials we need,
and because we'll have a lot of visitors,
we've ordered additional
automatic cleaning robots.
Emilia-sama!
I missed you, Emilia-sama!
Why did you come, Claudia?
I wanted to see you, so I requested it!
I told you that I'm "Emile"!
Emilia-sama!
I'm Emile!
Wendy!
Thanks for coming!
Reitia! Fritz!
It's been a while.
How's Ally?
I don't know.
I haven't seen her since that mission, either.
I see.
Anyway, it's nice to have you here.
Thanks.
Sakura?
She's not going to Karen's room?
Sorry I'm late.
Let's start our lessons.
Thank you.
Karen?
What?!
Nii-san, why are you here?
Oh, I'm sorry for scaring you.
Uh...
What are you all doing here?
Karen, you're going to sing
at Sakura's concert?!
That's right.
My secret weapon is Karen-chan.
But can Karen do it?
I mean, she's weak physically...
I've already taken that into consideration.
Karen-chan, show him.
Right.
Actually...
A Hundred!
It's named Divine Card.
She'll be able to jump and
fly around with this.
But I didn't think Karen
would be able to use a Hundred...
While we've been treating her,
she's developed an affinity
to the Hundred.
I didn't expect it either,
but she's got quite the knack for it.
Karen-chan's working really hard,
on both her Hundred training
and her singing lessons.
I want to do something
for people with my singing.
Just like Sakura-san's music gave me strength.
Karen...
B-But I've still got a long way to go...
I understand.
I'm sure you can do it.
Keep it up.
Yeah!
Why are you throwing me out?!
This place is off-limits while we're practicing.
You'll have to wait until the concert.
What...
It's now time for the second
Garden's Festa to begin!
Come on. This way.
I can't believe I have to man security here
during the whole Garden's Festa...
How terrible!
I wanted to have Emilia-sama
eat a chocolate banana!
Say, "Ah!"
Bite!
That's good!
And I can't do that!
I hate this universe!
Screw it.
Because it's the Garden's Festa today,
there's a lot of good food on the menu.
I'll bring some chocolate bananas
for dessert later.
They're having a festival now.
I wonder what everyone here is thinking.
We're the enemy.
They're not going to trick us.
All Slayers are the enemy.
I mean, they took our Hundreds.
But they didn't take Nesat's.
Because she wouldn't be able to see without it.
Why do you have your eyes?
You two need to get your act together!
Don't you remember what Vitaly said?
The Slayers are trying
to take over the world!
Finally, a break.
Hey, look at that, Hayato.
They're doing a ninja cafe over there.
And there's a zombie restaurant right there.
We can't stop everywhere.
We're going to Sakura's concert
after this, too.
I know.
Hey.
People are going to see us.
Just for a little bit.
Hayato! Emile!
Reitia! And Erica-san?!
Why are you two dressed like that?
I-I-It's not what you think.
Th-Th-There's a reason for this.
Noah and Xuemei recruited us for
this maid cafe during our break.
Th-They really needed help,
so we had to...
I see...
What do you think you're doing,
Emile Crossfode?!
I never thought I'd get to see
the vice president like this.
Such a rare find!
I'd better show the president, too!
Stop it, Emile Crossfode!
Still getting the shots!
Wait!
Delete that right now!
Don't wanna!
Hey!
Hey, Hayato, how about
you stop by with Emile?
Huh? By the maid cafe?
Two masters are here!
Hey.
Welcome back, Masters!
Th-This is pretty amazing.
Hey, Hayato.
Why are you getting all red?
Huh?
Do you like maids or something?
No, that's not it...
Hmph! If only I could
dress up like a girl, too...
How about you try it, then,
Emile Crossfode?
Huh?!
Oh, drag, huh?
That sounds like fun.
What are you saying?
I'm a guy! I can't wear a maid outfit!
It'll be fine, Crossfode-kun.
H-Hey, Hayato!
Save me!
Erica-san, this is bad.
If it gets out that Emile's a girl...
Huh?
You don't want to see?
It'll look good on her.
The contrast between
a short skirt and long hair...
The bright and enchanting "absolute territory"!
Here we are!
One new male maid, coming right up!
She looks like a real girl.
And we've got these huge boobs!
W-Wait!
These don't feel like you
made them with some towels!
Vice-President?!
Kisaragi Hayato, why don't
you cop a feel, too?
N-No, I'm...
Let go...
Why not? Go ahead and squeeze them.
Huh?
Give them a quick grab.
What?
Grab! Grab!
I couldn't...
What are you even talking about?
Grab! Grab! Grab!
You don't mind, do you,
Emile Crossfode?
Well, not if it's Hayato...
Grab! Grab!
Fine! Fine!
You really don't mind?
N-No...
Why are you hesitating, Kisaragi Hayato?
These are just towels...
Stop taking so long!
Huh? This...
...doesn't feel like a towel.
Hayato, that's...
...the real deal...
Huh?
Hey, wait!
What goes around comes around!
Wh-Why are you taking pictures?!
That was the tops.
I'm sending that to everyone.
I'm making my next doujin
into a "Haya x Emi" issue.
I see more rumors abound.
This is gonna be huge!
I actually don't mind rumors
being spread about us.
That isn't good, you know?
Could I get you two kissing next?
Hayato...
Vice President, do something about this!
Well, it's time for us to get back to work.
Let's go, Reitia Saintemilion.
Yeah, let's go.
H-Hey, Erica-san!
Erica-san!
It's finally time.
Sorry I'm late, Karen.
Nii-san, you came!
Well, I did promise to come see you.
Yeah!
So, Karen...
Are you going up on stage like that?
Yes. What about it?
Well, it's kind of...
...revealing?
Huh?
You're such a perv, Nii-san.
Don't say things like that
before my concert.
Well, I'm just kind of worried,
as your brother.
Now I'm kind of nervous.
Do something about it.
Fine.
Karen-chan.
Oh.
You're here, Hayato-kun.
Yeah. I wanted to wish Karen luck.
The concert will begin soon.
You're going on for the second song, Karen,
so you'll need to stand by in the wings.
Yes?
Sorry for the intrusion.
Judar-san!
Huh?
You mean from Warslarn?
I heard that the Diva, Kirishima Sakura,
was going to perform.
I came to wish you luck.
I think it's an honor that you'll
sing here at the Little Garden.
I hope you have a wonderful performance.
Thank you.
Also, Kisaragi Karen-kun.
You're Hayato-kun's sister, right?
Y-Yes.
I'm sure your song will
prove to be very powerful.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you!
I'll take my leave.
2... 1...
Sorry to keep you all waiting!
Here we go!
Hundred On!
Time to switch.
Oh, already?
Okay, thanks.
Sure.
That's all I need from you.
Good night.
Thank you all!
For our next song,
we have a special guest!
I wonder who it is.
Wh-Who knows?
This girl got me to love singing!
Everyone, give her a warm welcome!
Here she is!
Karen-chan?!
E-Everyone!
S-Sorry!
It's okay, Karen-chan.
R-Right!
Everyone, hi there!
Karen...
I mean,
my name is Kisaragi Karen.
I've been sick ever since I was young.
But I met Sakura-san,
heard her singing,
and gained the strength to
keep fighting my illness.
I have a dream now.
I want those who are sick like me,
or in a similar situation,
to hear my song.
And...
...I want to help other people
find their dreams, too.
This is the first step to my dream.
Hundred On!
That's Karen's Hundred.
Divine Card.
Garden's  Crisis